culturekings.com.au 2015-11-07

# Privacy Policy | Culture Kings Online Store

## What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

You are welcome to visit our site anonymously. However, when placing an order or registering with our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

## How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow cookies in your settings) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by [contacting customer service](http://www.culturekings.com.au/contacts/).

## Collection of computer data

When you visit Culture Kings, our company servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website. This data may include:

\- Your computer's IP address  
\- The type of browser that you are using  
\- The webpage you were visiting before you came to our site  
\- The pages within Culture Kings that you visit  
\- The time spent on those pages, items and information searched for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

This information is collected for analysis and evaluation in order to help us improve our site and the services and products we provide. This data will not be used in association with any other personal information.

## Google Analytics & Google AdWords Remarketing

Culture Kings use Analytics Remarketing with Google Analytics, and AdWords Remarketing with Google AdWords to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show Culture Kings ads on sites across the Internet. This could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Culture Kings website.

Culture Kings and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimise, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website, and to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.

Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network ads [HERE](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

You can also use this Analytics opt out tool [HERE](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions 

## Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Unsubscribing

Unsubscribing can be initiated at the link at the footer of each email,  by contacting us at info@culturekings.com.au, or by entering your email into <http://www.culturekings.com.au/unsubscribe> 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 07/04/14.

## Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Culture Kings  
[orders@culturekings.com.au  
](mailto:orders@culturekings.com.au)PO BOX 260  
ARCHERFIELD, QLD 4108 Australia  
(07) 3345 0522
